{
    "id": "acd274d4b6a44776b2130e0cb5180ecc",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The ………………………… speech went on for over an hour.",
            "description": "Grandiloquent means high sounding or pompous.",
            "answers": [
                "grandiose",
                "grant",
                "grandiloquent"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c1b2dc4b24f64e7aa9a99efafc64941c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The paintings show the ……………………………. of the royal palace in",
            "description": "Grandeur means magnificence. ",
            "answers": [
                "grandeur",
                "grandiose",
                "glamour"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "608baf531c034578ae8244f051daf6dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The government will ………………………….. land to anyone willing to farm it.",
            "description": "To grant is to give. Grand means majestic or impressive.",
            "answers": [
                "grant",
                "grand",
                "grandiose"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "247f69965e6f47e0b1803ce23cf0211c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not …………………………… enough to be a good hostess.",
            "description": "Gracious means affable or courteous. Graceful means lissome or supple.",
            "answers": [
                "graceful",
                "gracious",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bbe942775dd34667a22d922e1c22125b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Helping the poor gives her tremendous ……………………………",
            "description": "Gratification means satisfaction. Gratitude means thankful.",
            "answers": [
                "gratitude",
                "gratuitous",
                "gratification"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bbe9577f51764c3aa68b304c349b351c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The wet leaves ………………………… towards the bottom of the pool.",
            "description": "Gravitate means fall, sink or descend.",
            "answers": [
                "graft",
                "gravitate",
                "grate"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8783427d96bd454ba65be3b2ad1fc894"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am indebted to you for your ……………………………. help.",
            "description": "Gratuitous means voluntary or spontaneous.",
            "answers": [
                "gratitude",
                "gratuitous",
                "gracious"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a78466256bff476ba894a8ae565b5c1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The candle made only a ……………………… in the vast room",
            "description": "A glimmer is a small glow. A glimpse is a brief look.",
            "answers": [
                "glimmer",
                "glitter",
                "glimpse"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "04941a90bb104a709702b4d093349d5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Good winners don’t ………………………….. over their victory.",
            "description": "To gloat over something is to revel in it.",
            "answers": [
                "bloat",
                "gloat",
                "clot"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "feeb926d209e478a8207c66e278c8cbd"
        },
        {
            "question": "This bill contains a ………………………….. error in addition.",
            "description": "Glaring means conspicuous, blatant",
            "answers": [
                "blaring",
                "flaring",
                "glaring"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0f2ec594d85e46ba8143531e9713f533"
        },
        {
            "question": "With some words missing and others misspelled, the message was pure ……………………………",
            "description": "Gibberish means senseless writing or meaningless talk.",
            "answers": [
                "gibe",
                "gibberish",
                "garble"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c1474968d0b740a6aabcafb5febc76d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The driver …………………………… for the police car to stop.",
            "description": "Gesticulate means gesture or signal.",
            "answers": [
                "germinated",
                "gesticulated"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "276d6430e08f466eb25796024d2056d3"
        }
    ]
}